{
    "id": "f1ee140975b7414e876905edc2b2335d",
    "title": "Grammar Check",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Words used to modify nouns are called …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adverb",
                "adjective",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "321435991a9e4fe88185b4ec476bff58"
        },
        {
            "question": "Adverbs can modify verbs, adjectives and other adverbs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b93a5e4759ff424b96251a8393f02d25"
        },
        {
            "question": "The present perfect tense can be used with past time adverbs like yesterday and last week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "445e969d2fe84043b2d3efec4e883d9e"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the simple present tense, we use did to make questions and negatives.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "442c457e61404b4289da3da9663feb72"
        },
        {
            "question": "The present continuous tense can be used to talk about future events.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "72408f644ca14b61a253bfa0fed160e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Modal auxiliaries do not have infinitives or –ing forms.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "524070af976b47bdbf0a4cd1da6c21ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "We cannot use the article a/an with uncountable nouns.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "abc129b3183941dfaafa1794d0968e85"
        },
        {
            "question": "When enough modifies a noun, it goes after it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1f54f5c00c65408d8512a111bd94bc1b"
        },
        {
            "question": "We need two conjunctions to join two clauses.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c487e923e454300bad3f54cbd5093ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "Prepositions can go at the end of a sentence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dbde09087a534a908dba9037cf0e8c43"
        },
        {
            "question": "Proper nouns always begin with a capital letter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "075e5a4fe89b487892ce011f8c016f03"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following can be used to join two clauses?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Conjunctions",
                "Relative pronouns",
                "Relative adverbs",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "67500d16533a406f8733a53aa859da65"
        }
    ]
}